{
  "question": "What Role Do You Want to Play?",
  "options": [
    {
      "answer": "Support",
      "question": "How Complex Should the Hero Be?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Pretty Simple",
          "question": "Do You Want To Be Support Every Single Time?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "I Could Try Offlane?",
              "question": "Stun?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "None For Me, Thanks!",
                  "question": "Healing?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "None For Me, Thanks!",
                      "question": "Name Your Plague",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Poison",
                          "character": "venomancer"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Zombies",
                          "character": "undying"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "omniknight"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Yes, Please",
                  "question": "What Should Your Ult Do?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Gambling",
                      "character": "ogre_magi"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Massive Damage",
                      "character": "lion"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Big Stun",
                      "character": "spirit_breaker"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "I Could Try Mid",
              "question": "How Many Stuns Do You Want?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "None",
                  "question": "Save Your Team or Murder Enemies?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "I Like Murder",
                      "character": "skywrath_mage"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Save Allies",
                      "character": "dazzle"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Some",
                  "question": "Do You Want the Option to Build Right Click Damage?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "character": "witch_doctor"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "snapfire"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Lots",
                  "question": "Stay Way Back or Jump In?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Stay Back",
                      "character": "jakiro"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Jump In",
                      "character": "crystal_maiden"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "I Could Try Carry",
              "question": "When Do You Want To Be Strongest?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Early/Midgame",
                  "character": "vengefulspirit"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Late Game",
                  "character": "Silencer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Yes",
              "question": "Specialty?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Lane Dominator",
                  "character": "Lich"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Stuns",
                  "character": "shadow_shaman"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Pushing Towers",
                  "character": "warlock"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Complex",
          "question": "How Versatile Should the Hero Be?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Very Versatile",
              "question": "Melee or Ranged?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Ranged",
                  "question": "Are You Addicted to Barely Escaping With Your Life?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "Do You Want to Be Kinda Durable?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Nah, I'm Good",
                          "character": "ancient_apparition"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "enchantress"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "Gotta Go Fast?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "hoodwink"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "dark_willow"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Melee",
                  "question": "You wanna be a Chunky Boi?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "You a Thief?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "Marci"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "bounty_hunter"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "Dota's Most Popular Hero?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "pudge"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "tusk"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Somewhat Versatile",
              "question": "Melee or Ranged?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Melee",
                  "question": "How Many Stuns Do You Want?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "None",
                      "character": "dark_seer"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No Stun But a Big Root",
                      "character": "treant_protector"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Plenty",
                      "character": "clockwerk"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "All of Them",
                      "character": "earthshaker"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Ranged",
                  "question": "Do You Want Everyone to Hate You?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "How Do You Feel About Skillshots?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "No Thx",
                          "character": "winter_wyvern"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Love em",
                          "character": "mirana"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "You Like Bombs??",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "techies"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "pugna"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "I Just Wanna Do My One Thing",
              "question": "And What is That One Thing?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Teamfighting",
                  "question": "Do You Want to Be At All Useful When Your Ult is on Cooldown?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "character": "enigma"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "phoenix"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Completely Shutting Down One Guy",
                  "question": "By...",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Stunning Them",
                      "character": "bane"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Killing Them",
                      "character": "nyx_assassin"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Being a Total Lane Bully",
                  "question": "...with a dash of...",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Lighting",
                      "character": "disruptor"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Paint",
                      "character": "grimstroke"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Very Complex",
          "question": "Do You Want to Control a Bunch of Creeps?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Yes",
              "question": "Do You Want the Option to Become a Carry?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "character": "chen"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "character": "furion"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "No",
              "question": "What's Your Main Goal?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Heal Allies",
                  "question": "Do You Want to Cast a Lot of Spells?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "character": "io"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "oracle"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Disrupt Enemies",
                  "question": "Turn Your Enemies' Power Against Them?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "Wizard or Demon?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Wizard",
                          "character": "rubick"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Demon",
                          "character": "shadow_demon"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "Melee or Ranged?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Melee",
                          "character": "earth_spirit"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Ranged",
                          "character": "keeper_of_the_light"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "Offlane",
      "question": "How Complex Should the Hero Be?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Very Complex",
          "character": "brewmaster"
        },
        {
          "answer": "Complex",
          "question": "How Tanky Do You Want To Be?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Extremely",
              "question": "How Versatile Should The Hero Be?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Zero",
                  "character": "shredder"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "A Little Bit",
                  "character": "primal_beast"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Pretty Versatile",
                  "character": "abyssal_underlord"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Very",
              "question": "Mess Up The Whole Enemy Team or Just Hate One Guy?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "I Hate That Guy",
                  "character": "doom_bringer"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Whole Team",
                  "question": "Do You Want a Ghost Buddy?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "elder_titan"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "character": "magnataur"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Somewhat",
              "question": "What Do You Want to Summon?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Wolves",
                  "character": "lycan"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Boars and Birds",
                  "character": "beastmaster"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Sand",
                  "character": "sand_king"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Pretty Simple",
          "question": "Do YOu Wnat to Play Offlane Every Time?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "I Could Try Support",
              "character": "abaddon"
            },
            {
              "answer": "I Could Try Carry",
              "character": "bristleback"
            },
            {
              "answer": "I Could Try Mid",
              "character": "dragon_knight"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Yes",
              "question": "Do You Want To Be an Absolute Tank?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "question": "Should Enemies Die for The Crime of Daring to Even Attack You?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "Spin to Win?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "axe"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "centaur"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "How Do You Feel About Fish?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Huh??",
                          "character": "Mars"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "I Like Them More Than People",
                          "character": "tidehunter"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "question": "Fill in the Blank: I Want to Fight ___",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "At Night",
                      "character": "night_stalker"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "In the River",
                      "character": "slardar"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Anything That Moves",
                      "character": "legion_commander"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "How About EVERY Role?",
              "character": "dawnbreaker"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mid",
      "question": "How Complex Should the Hero Be?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Unga Bunga",
          "character": "huskar"
        },
        {
          "answer": "Pretty Simple",
          "question": "Do You Want to Push Towers?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Yes",
              "question": "You Want Stuns?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "character": "leshrac"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "character": "death_prophet"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "No",
              "question": "How Quickly Do You Want to Kill Your Enemies?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "2 Seconds",
                  "character": "zuus"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Quick But Not Unreasonable",
                  "character": "necrolyte"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "When I Get Around to It",
                  "character": "viper"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Maybe",
              "question": "Do You Wnat to Attack Fast or Run Fast?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Attacking",
                  "character": "lina"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Zooming",
                  "character": "razor"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Complex",
          "question": "Melee or Ranged?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Melee",
              "question": "Do You Want to Knock Down Towers All Day?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "question": "Do You Have Arachnophobia?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "lone_druid"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "character": "broodmother"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "question": "In Fights, Do You Want to Stun Everybody or Zip Around?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Zippy!",
                      "question": "Red or Purple?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Red",
                          "character": "ember_spirit"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Purple",
                          "character": "void_spirit"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Stun",
                      "question": "Do You Want To Be a Pirate?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "kunkka"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes and Also I Want To Be French",
                          "character": "pangolier"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "question": "Still Wrong. Do You Want To Be a Pirate?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Yes",
                              "character": "kunkka"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Yes and Also I Want To Be French",
                              "character": "pangolier"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Ranged",
              "question": "Be Honest. How Big is Your EGO?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Big",
                  "character": "storm_spirit"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Enomous",
                  "character": "nevermore"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Big and Also I Hate You",
                  "character": "obsidian_devourer"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "I Would Say Normal Size",
                  "question": "Do You Want to Teleport Around?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "Do You Want to Stun People?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "batrider"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "templar_assassin"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Maybe a Little",
                          "character": "winrunner"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "Do You Want to Just Blast People?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "queen_of_pain"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Maybe a Little",
                          "character": "puck"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Very Complex",
          "question": "How Many Units Do You Want to Control?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "2",
              "character": "arc_warden"
            },
            {
              "answer": "3",
              "character": "visage"
            },
            {
              "answer": "5",
              "character": "meepo"
            },
            {
              "answer": "1",
              "question": "Magic or Science?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Magic",
                  "character": "invoker"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Science",
                  "character": "tinker"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "Carry",
      "question": "How Complex Should the Hero Be?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Very Complex",
          "character": "morphling"
        },
        {
          "answer": "Complex",
          "question": "Melee or Ranged?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Melee",
              "question": "Do You Want to Be Carry Every Single Time?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "I Could Try Mid As Well",
                  "question": "What About Support?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Not a Chance",
                      "character": "alchemist"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I'll Try Whatever!",
                      "question": "How Do You Want to Get Your Kills?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Brute Force",
                          "character": "tiny"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Style on em",
                          "character": "monkey_king"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "question": "Do You Like Illusions?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "What About Stuns?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Stuns Are For the Weak",
                          "character": "phantom_lancer"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Cant Go Wrong With a Good Stun",
                          "character": "naga_siren"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "Do You Want To Be a Tank?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "question": "Do You Want to 1v1 or Teamfight?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "1v1",
                              "character": "lifestealer"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Teamfight",
                              "character": "spectre"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "question": "Do You Want a Massive Teamfight Ult?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Yes",
                              "character": "faceless_void"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Dont Need One",
                              "character": "slark"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Ranged",
              "question": "Do You Like to Go Invisible?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "question": "Do You Want to Push Towers?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "character": "clinkz"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "character": "weaver"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "question": "Physical Damange or Magical Damage?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Physical",
                      "character": "gyrocopter"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Magic",
                      "character": "muerta"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "I Cant Decide",
              "question": "Whats Your Strategy?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Im Very Calculated and Precise",
                  "character": "terrorblade"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Haha Axes Go BRRRR",
                  "character": "troll_warlord"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Pretty Simple",
          "question": "Melee or Ranged?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Ranged",
              "question": "If Your Attacks Could Have an Extra Effect, What Would It Be?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Bouncy",
                  "character": "luna"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "1 Mile of Range",
                  "character": "sniper"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Freeze People",
                  "character": "drow_ranger"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Hit Everyone In Sight",
                  "character": "medusa"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Melee",
              "question": "Do You Want the Option to Be a Support Sometimes?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "character": "riki"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "question": "Do You Want a Short-Range Teleport Ability?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "And Evasion?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "character": "phantom_assassin"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "character": "antimage"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "question": "Do You Want to Go into a Rage?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yes",
                          "question": "Do You Want to Absolutely Murder Roshan?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Yes",
                              "character": "ursa"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "A Little Bit",
                              "character": "sven"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "No",
                          "question": "Do You Want To Be a Tank?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Yes",
                              "question": "What Would You Like to Summon",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Illusions",
                                  "character": "chaos_knight"
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "Skeletons",
                                  "character": "skeleton_king"
                                }
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "No",
                              "question": "Do You Want to Make Race Car Noises While Playing?",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Yes",
                                  "character": "bloodseeker"
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "No",
                                  "character": "juggernaut"
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}